B1.
Nora is listening to a podcast about how to make potato stamps.
Listen to it and put the following instructions in the correct order.
Write the numbers 1 to 7 in the blanks.
Today we're going to make potato stamps.
Potato stamps are very easy to make.
First, you should get a large potato.
Don't use a small one, it'll be too difficult to hold.
Next, wash it carefully.
You should be sure to get it really clean.
Now cut it in half with a knife.
Be careful, I don't want anyone to get hurt.
Next, you should draw a design on the flat side of the potato with a pen.
Then carefully cut the design out with your knife.
After that, put some paint on a plate.
Put the flat side of your potato in the paint.
Finally, put the potato on a piece of paper.
Isn't that fun?
You have a potato stamp now.